q_set = {"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBxdW90ZSBmcm9tIHRoZSAxOTQyIGZpbG0gQ2FzYWJsYW5jYT8g","correct_answer":"IkZyYW5rbHksIG15IGRlYXIsIEkgZG9uJ3QgZ2l2ZSBhIGRhbW4uIg==","incorrect_answers":["IkhlcmUncyBsb29raW4nIGF0IHlvdSwga2lkLiI=","4oCcT2YgYWxsIHRoZSBnaW4gam9pbnRzLCBpbiBhbGwgdGhlIHRvd25zLCBpbiBhbGwgdGhlIHdvcmxkLCBzaGUgd2Fsa3MgaW50byBtaW5l4oCm4oCd","IlJvdW5kIHVwIHRoZSB1c3VhbCBzdXNwZWN0cy4i"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgYSAnQm9uZCBHaXJsJz8g","correct_answer":"VmFuZXNzYSBLZW5zaW5ndG9u","incorrect_answers":["UGFtIEJvdXZpZXI=","TWFyeSBHb29kbmlnaHQ=","V2FpIExpbg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggbW92aWUgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gMjAxNiBmZWF0dXJlcyBTdXBlcm1hbiBhbmQgQmF0bWFuIGZpZ2h0aW5nPw==","correct_answer":"QmF0bWFuIHYgU3VwZXJtYW46IERhd24gb2YgSnVzdGljZQ==","incorrect_answers":["QmF0bWFuIHYgU3VwZXJtYW46IFN1cGVyYXBvY2FseXBzZQ==","QmF0bWFuIHYgU3VwZXJtYW46IEJsYWNrIG9mIEtuaWdodA==","QmF0bWFuIHYgU3VwZXJtYW46IEtuaWdodGZhbGw="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBuYW1lIGRpZCBUb20gSGFua3MgZ2l2ZSB0byBoaXMgdm9sbGV5YmFsbCBjb21wYW5pb24gaW4gdGhlIGZpbG0gYENhc3QgQXdheWA\/","correct_answer":"V2lsc29u","incorrect_answers":["RnJpZGF5","Sm9uZXM=","QmlsbHk="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllIOKAnFRoZSBJcm9uIEdpYW50LOKAnSB0aGlzIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpcyB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qu","correct_answer":"SG9nYXJ0aCBIdWdoZXM=","incorrect_answers":["S2VudCBNYW5zbGV5","RGVhbiBNY0NvcHBpbg==","QW5uaWUgSHVnaGVz"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaGlnaGVzdCBncm9zc2luZyBmaWxtIG9mIGFsbCB0aW1lICh3aXRob3V0IGFkanVzdGluZyBmb3IgaW5mbGF0aW9uKT8=","correct_answer":"QXZhdGFy","incorrect_answers":["SnVyYXNzaWMgV29ybGQ=","U3RhciBXYXJzOiBUaGUgRm9yY2UgQXdha2Vucw==","VGl0YW5pYw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"SW4gdGhlIGZpbG0gIkludGVyc3RlbGxhciIsIGhvdyBsb25nIGRpZCB0aGV5IHNwZW5kIG9uIE1pbGxlcidzIHBsYW5ldD8=","correct_answer":"MjMgeWVhcnMsIDQgbW9udGhzLCBhbmQgOCBkYXlz","incorrect_answers":["MTUgeWVhcnMsIDIgbW9udGhzLCBhbmQgMTUgZGF5cw==","MTAgbW9udGhzIGFuZCA2IGRheXM=","MjYgeWVhcnMsIDQgbW9udGhzLCBhbmQgMTAgZGF5cw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"SW4gdGhlIDE5NzYgZmlsbSAnVGF4aSBEcml2ZXInLCBob3cgbWFueSBndW5zIGRpZCBUcmF2aXMgYnV5IGZyb20gdGhlIHNhbGVzbWFuPw==","correct_answer":"NA==","incorrect_answers":["Mg==","Ng==","MQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hpY2ggcmV0aXJlZCBBbWVyaWNhbiBmb290YmFsbCBxdWFydGVyYmFjayBwbGF5ZWQgaGltc2VsZiBpbiAnQWNlIFZlbnR1cmE6IFBldCBEZXRlY3RpdmUnIGFuZCAnTGl0dGxlIE5pY2t5Jz8=","correct_answer":"RGFuIE1hcmlubw==","incorrect_answers":["Sm9obiBFbHdheQ==","VG9tIEJyYWR5","Sm9lIE1vbnRhbmE="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIHBsYXllZCBEZXB1dHkgTWFyc2hhbCBTYW11ZWwgR2VyYXJkIGluIHRoZSAxOTkzIGZpbG0gIlRoZSBGdWdpdGl2ZSI\/","correct_answer":"VG9tbXkgTGVlIEpvbmVz","incorrect_answers":["SGFycmlzb24gRm9yZA==","SGFydmV5IEtlaXRlbA==","TWFydGluIExhbmRhdQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBkYW5jZWQgdGhlIHR3aXN0IHdpdGggSm9obiBUcmF2b2x0YSBpbiAnUHVscCBGaWN0aW9uJz8=","correct_answer":"VW1hIFRodXJtYW4=","incorrect_answers":["S2F0aHkgR3JpZmZpbg==","UGFtIEdyaWVy","QnJpZGdldCBGb25kYQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hvIHZvaWNlZCB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIERyYWNvIGluIHRoZSAxOTk2IG1vdmllICdEcmFnb25IZWFydCc\/","correct_answer":"U2VhbiBDb25uZXJ5","incorrect_answers":["RGVubmlzIFF1YWlk","UGV0ZSBQb3N0bGV0aHdhaXRl","QnJpYW4gVGhvbXBzb24="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"SW4gdGhlIDE5ODQgbW92aWUgIlRoZSBUZXJtaW5hdG9yIiwgd2hhdCBtb2RlbCBudW1iZXIgaXMgdGhlIFRlcm1pbmF0b3IgcG9ydHJheWVkIGJ5IEFybm9sZCBTY2h3YXJ6ZW5lZ2dlcj8=","correct_answer":"VC04MDA=","incorrect_answers":["SS05NTA=","VC04ODg=","VC0xMDAw"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hpY2ggYWN0b3IgcGxheWVkIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiB0aGUgMTk5MCBmaWxtICJFZHdhcmQgU2Npc3NvcmhhbmRzIj8=","correct_answer":"Sm9obm55IERlcHA=","incorrect_answers":["IENsaW50IEVhc3R3b29k","TGVvbmFyZG8gRGlDYXByaW8=","QmVuIFN0aWxsZXI="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggbW92aWUgY29udGFpbnMgdGhlIHF1b3RlLCAiU2F5IGhlbGxvIHRvIG15IGxpdHRsZSBmcmllbmQhIj8=","correct_answer":"U2NhcmZhY2U=","incorrect_answers":["UmVzZXJ2b2lyIERvZ3M=","SGVhdA==","R29vZGZlbGxhcw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGRpcmVjdGVkIHRoZSBtb3ZpZXMgIlB1bHAgRmljdGlvbiIsICJSZXNlcnZvaXIgRG9ncyIgYW5kICJEamFuZ28gVW5jaGFpbmVkIj8=","correct_answer":"UXVlbnRpbiBUYXJhbnRpbm8=","incorrect_answers":["TWFydGluIFNjb3JjZXNl","U3RldmVuIFNwaWVsYmVyZw==","SmFtZXMgQ2FtZXJvbg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGRpcmVjdGVkIHRoZSAyMDE1IG1vdmllICJUaGUgUmV2ZW5hbnQiPw==","correct_answer":"QWxlamFuZHJvIEcuIEnDscOhcnJpdHU=","incorrect_answers":["Q2hyaXN0b3BoZXIgTm9sYW4=","RGF2aWQgRmluY2hlcg==","V2VzIEFuZGVyc29u"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgRG9yb3RoeSdzIHN1cm5hbWUgaW4gJ1RoZSBXaXphcmQgT2YgT3onPw==","correct_answer":"R2FsZQ==","incorrect_answers":["UGVya2lucw==","RGF5","UGFya2Vy"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBKYW1lcyBCb25kIHZpbGxhaW5zIGlzIG5vdCBhZmZpbGlhdGVkIHdpdGggdGhlIFNQRUNUUkUgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uPw==","correct_answer":"QXVyaWMgR29sZGZpbmdlcg==","incorrect_answers":["RHIuIEp1bGl1cyBObw==","Um9zYSBLbGViYg==","RW1pbGlvIExhcmdv"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhpcyBtb3ZpZSBjb250YWlucyB0aGUgcXVvdGUsICJJIGZlZWwgdGhlIG5lZWQgLi4uIHRoZSBuZWVkIGZvciBzcGVlZCEi","correct_answer":"VG9wIEd1bg==","incorrect_answers":["RGF5cyBvZiBUaHVuZGVy","VGhlIENvbG9yIG9mIE1vbmV5","Q29ja3RhaWw="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhpcyBtb3ZpZSBjb250YWlucyB0aGUgcXVvdGUsICJOb2JvZHkgcHV0cyBCYWJ5IGluIGEgY29ybmVyLiI=","correct_answer":"RGlydHkgRGFuY2luZw==","incorrect_answers":["VGhyZWUgTWVuIGFuZCBhIEJhYnk=","RmVycmlzIEJ1ZWxsZXIncyBEYXkgT2Zm","UHJldHR5IGluIFBpbms="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"VGhpcyBtb3ZpZSBjb250YWlucyB0aGUgcXVvdGUsICJXaGF0IHdlJ3ZlIGdvdCBoZXJlIGlzIGEgZmFpbHVyZSB0byBjb21tdW5pY2F0ZS4i","correct_answer":"Q29vbCBIYW5kIEx1a2U=","incorrect_answers":["Qm9ubmllIGFuZCBDbHlkZQ==","VGhlIEdyYWR1YXRl","SW4gdGhlIEhlYXQgb2YgdGhlIE5pZ2h0"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"SW4gd2hpY2ggQWZyaWNhbiBjb3VudHJ5IHdhcyB0aGUgMjAwNiBmaWxtICdCbG9vZCBEaWFtb25kJyBtb3N0bHkgc2V0IGluPw==","correct_answer":"U2llcnJhIExlb25l","incorrect_answers":["TGliZXJpYQ==","QnVya2luYSBGYXNv","Q2VudHJhbCBBZnJpY2FuIFJlcHVibGlj"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hhdCBkb2VzIFRJRSBzdGFuZCBmb3IgaW4gcmVmZXJlbmNlIHRvIHRoZSBUSUUgRmlnaHRlciBpbiAiU3RhciBXYXJzIj8=","correct_answer":"VHdpbiBJb24gRW5naW5l","incorrect_answers":["VHdpbiBJcm9uIEVuZ2luZQ==","VHdpbiBJbnRlcmNlcHRlciBFbmdpbmU=","VHdpbiBJbmNlcHRpb24gRW5naW5l"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgYXNzYXNzaW4gaW4gdGhlIGZpcnN0ICJIZWxsYm95IiBtb3ZpZT8=","correct_answer":"S2FybCBSdXByZWNodCBLcm9lbmVu","incorrect_answers":["S2xhdXMgV2VybmVyIHZvbiBLcnVwdA==","R3JpZ29yaSBFZmltb3ZpY2ggUmFzcHV0aW4=","SWxzYSBIYXVwc3RlaW4="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hhdCBkaWQgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG1vdmluZyBwaWN0dXJlIGRlcGljdD8=","correct_answer":"QSBnYWxsb3BpbmcgaG9yc2U=","incorrect_answers":["QSB3b21hbiBpbiBhIGRyZXNz","QSBtYW4gd2Fsa2luZw==","QSBjcmFja2xpbmcgZmlyZQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hpY2ggbW92aWUgc2VxdWVsIGhhZCBpbXByb3ZlZCBib3ggb2ZmaWNlIHJlc3VsdHMgY29tcGFyZWQgdG8gaXRzIG9yaWdpbmFsIGZpbG0\/","correct_answer":"VG95IFN0b3J5IDI=","incorrect_answers":["U2luIENpdHk6IEEgRGFtZSB0byBLaWxsIEZvcg==","U3BlZWQgMjogQ3J1aXNlIENvbnRyb2w=","U29uIG9mIHRoZSBNYXNr"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hpY2ggaWNvbmljIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiBtb3ZpZXMgc3VjaCBhcyAiVGhlIEVuZm9yY2VyIiwgIlN1ZGRlbiBJbXBhY3QiLCBhbmQgIlRoZSBEZWFkIFBvb2wiPw==","correct_answer":"RGlydHkgSGFycnk=","incorrect_answers":["SW5kaWFuYSBKb25lcw==","SmFtZXMgQm9uZA==","SGFycnkgUG90dGVy"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hvIHBsYXlzIHRoZSBOZW1lc2lzIGluIHRoZSBSZXNpZGVudCBFdmlsIG1vdmllcz8=","correct_answer":"TWF0dGhldyBUYXlsb3I=","incorrect_answers":["SmFzb24gRGlw","RXJpYyBNYWJpdXM=","SmltbXkgTWF0dHM="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"SW4gd2hhdCBEaXNuZXkgbW92aWUgY2FuIHlvdSBzcG90IHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgIlBhYy1NYW4iIGluIGlmIHlvdSBsb29rIGNsb3NlbHkgZW5vdWdoIGluIHNvbWUgc2NlbmVzPw==","correct_answer":"VHJvbg==","incorrect_answers":["QmlnIEhlcm8gNg==","RmFudGFzaWE=","TW9uc3RlcnMsIEluYy4="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"VGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHZpbGxpYW4gaW4gdGhlIDIwMTUgUnVzc2lhbi1BbWVyaWNhbiBTY2ktRmkgTW92aWUgIkhhcmRjb3JlIEhlbnJ5IiBpcy4uLg==","correct_answer":"QWthbg==","incorrect_answers":["RXN0ZWxsZQ==","SmltbXk=","SGVucnk="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"SW4gdGhlIDE5NzkgQnJpdGlzaCBmaWxtICJRdWFkcm9waGVuaWEiIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIG1haW4gcHJvdGFnb25pc3Q\/","correct_answer":"SmltbXkgQ29vcGVy","incorrect_answers":["UGV0ZSBUb3duc2hlbmQ=","RnJhbmMgUm9kZGFt","QXJjaGllIEJ1bmtlcg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGZpbG1zIGFyZSBzaG90IGVudGlyZWx5IGluIG9uZS10YWtlPw==","correct_answer":"UnVzc2lhbiBBcms=","incorrect_answers":["R29vZCBXaWxsIEh1bnRpbmc=","QmlyZG1hbg==","U2NoaW5kbGVyJ3MgTGlzdA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllICJDYXN0IEF3YXkiIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0J3MgYmVzdCBmcmllbmQgd2hpbGUgb24gdGhlIGlzbGFuZCBpcyBuYW1lZA==","correct_answer":"V2lsc29u","incorrect_answers":["Q2Fyc29u","SmFja3Nvbg==","V2lsbHk="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBwaHJhc2UgZm9yIHRoZSBMYXRpbiBzYXlpbmcgIlJvbWFuZXMgRXVudCBEb211cyIgaW4gTW9udHkgUHl0aG9uJ3MgTGlmZSBvZiBCcmlhbj8=","correct_answer":"Um9tYW5pIEl0ZSBEb211bQ==","incorrect_answers":["Um9tYW5zIEdvIEhvbWU=","Um94YW5pIEl0ZSBEb211bQ==","VG9tYXRlIEl0ZSBEb211bQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hvIHBsYXllZCBTZ3QuIEdvcmRvbiBFbGlhcyBpbiAnUGxhdG9vbicgKDE5ODYpPw==","correct_answer":"V2lsbGVtIERhZm9l","incorrect_answers":["Q2hhcmxpZSBTaGVlbg==","TWF0dCBEYW1vbg==","Sm9obm55IERlcHA="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gIkp1cmFzc2ljIFdvcmxkIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZGlub3NhdXIgdGhhdCBpcyBhIGdlbmV0aWMgaHlicmlkPw==","correct_answer":"SW5kb21pbnVzIFJleA==","incorrect_answers":["TW9zYXNhdXJ1cw==","UHRlcmFub2Rvbg==","VHlyYW5ub3NhdXJ1cyBSZXgg"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllICJTY3JlYW0iIHdobyBpcyBHaG9zdCBGYWNlPw==","correct_answer":"QmlsbHkgTG9vbWlzIGFuZCBTdHUgTWFjaGVy","incorrect_answers":["RGV3ZXkgUmlsZXk=","U2lkbmV5IFByZXNjb3R0","QXJjaGllIFByZXNjb3R0IGFuZCBQaGlsaXAgTWFydg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"SW4gdGhlIDE5OTkgbW92aWUgRmlnaHQgQ2x1Yiwgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgcnVsZSBvZiB0aGUgImZpZ2h0IGNsdWIiPw==","correct_answer":"QWx3YXlzIHdlYXIgYSBzaGlydA==","incorrect_answers":["WW91IGRvIG5vdCB0YWxrIGFib3V0IEZJR0hUIENMVUI=","T25seSB0d28gZ3V5cyB0byBhIGZpZ2h0","RmlnaHRzIHdpbGwgZ28gb24gYXMgbG9uZyBhcyB0aGV5IGhhdmUgdG8="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG1vbnN0ZXIgdG8gYXBwZWFyIGFsb25nc2lkZSBHb2R6aWxsYT8=","correct_answer":"QW5ndWlydXM=","incorrect_answers":["S2luZyBLb25n","TW90aHJh","S2luZyBHaGlkb3Jh"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllIEdyZW1saW5zLCBhZnRlciB3aGF0IHRpbWUgb2YgZGF5IHNob3VsZCB5b3Ugbm90IGZlZWQgTW9nd2FpPw==","correct_answer":"TWlkbmlnaHQ=","incorrect_answers":["RXZlbmluZw==","TW9ybmluZw==","QWZ0ZXJub29u"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIDE5OTIgZmlsbSAiQXJteSBvZiBEYXJrbmVzcyIsIHdoYXQgbmFtZSBkb2VzIEFzaCBnaXZlIHRvIGhpcyBkb3VibGUtYmFycmVsZWQgc2hvdGd1bj8=","correct_answer":"Qm9vbXN0aWNr","incorrect_answers":["Qmxvb21zdGljaw==","Qmxhc3RicmFuY2g=","Mi1QdW1wIENodW1w"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"SW4gd2hpY2ggbW92aWUgZG9lcyBSb2JpbiBXaWxsaWFtcycgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGhhdmUgdG8gZGlzZ3Vpc2UgdGhlbXNlbHZlcyBpbnRvIGEgd29tYW4\/","correct_answer":"TXJzLiBEb3VidGZpcmU=","incorrect_answers":["T2xkIERvZ3M=","SnVtYW5qaQ==","QXdha2VuaW5ncw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGNoZWVzZSwgbG92ZWQgYnkgV2FsbGFjZSBhbmQgR3JvbWl0LCBoYWQgaXQncyBzYWxlIHByaWNlcyByaXNlIGFmdGVyIHRoZWlyIHN1Y2Nlc3NmdWwgc2hvcnQgZmlsbXM\/","correct_answer":"V2Vuc2xleWRhbGU=","incorrect_answers":["Q2hlZGRhcg==","TW9vbiBDaGVlc2U=","RWRhbQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllICJCbGFkZSBSdW5uZXIiLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSB0ZXJtIHVzZWQgZm9yIGh1bWFuLWxpa2UgYW5kcm9pZHMgPw==","correct_answer":"UmVwbGljYW50cw==","incorrect_answers":["Q3lsb25z","U3ludGhldGljcw==","U2tpbmpvYnM="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIHNpbmdlciB3YXMgcG9ydHJheWVkIGJ5IGFjdG9yIEtldmluIFNwYWNleSBpbiB0aGUgMjAwNCBiaW9ncmFwaGljYWwgZmlsbSAiQmV5b25kIHRoZSBTZWEiPw==","correct_answer":"Qm9iYnkgRGFyaW4=","incorrect_answers":["TG91aXMgQXJtc3Ryb25n","RnJhbmsgU2luYXRyYQ==","RGVhbiBNYXJ0aW4="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIDE5OTUgZmlsbSAiQmFsdG8iLCB3aG8gYXJlIFN0ZWVsZSdzIGFjY29tcGxpY2VzPw==","correct_answer":"S2FsdGFnLCBOaWtraSwgYW5kIFN0YXI=","incorrect_answers":["RHVzdHksIEtpcmJ5LCBhbmQgUmFscGg=","TnVrLCBZYWssIGFuZCBTdW1hYw==","SmVubmEsIFN5bHZpZSwgYW5kIERpeGll"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"SW4gb3JkZXIgdG8gY3V0IGNvc3RzLCB3aGF0IHdlcmUgbW9zdCBvZiB0aGUgZXh0cmFzIG9mIE1hZCBNYXggKDE5NzkpIHBhaWQgd2l0aD8=","correct_answer":"QmVlcg==","incorrect_answers":["RmFzdCBmb29k","Rm9vZCBzdGFtcHM=","VGhleSB3ZXJlbid0IHBhaWQ="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFrZSBhbmQgbW9kZWwgb2YgdGhlIHRvdXIgdmVoaWNsZXMgaW4gIkp1cmFzc2ljIFBhcmsiPw==","correct_answer":"MTk5MiBGb3JkIEV4cGxvcmVyIFhMVA==","incorrect_answers":["MTk5MiBUb3lvdGEgTGFuZCBDcnVpc2Vy","MTk5MiBKZWVwIFdyYW5nbGVyIFlKIFNhaGFy","TWVyY2VkZXMgTS1DbGFzcw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"bWVkaXVt","question":"SW4gIkp1cmFzc2ljIFdvcmxkIiwgd2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBwdXJjaGFzZXMgSW5HZW4gYW5kIGNyZWF0ZXMgSnVyYXNzaWMgV29ybGQ\/","correct_answer":"TWFzcmFuaSBHbG9iYWwgQ29ycG9yYXRpb24g","incorrect_answers":["QmlvbG9neSBTeW50aGV0aWNzIFRlY2hub2xvZ2llcw==","SW50ZXJuYXRpb25hbCBHZW5ldGljcyBJbmNvcnBvcmF0ZWQ=","SW50ZXJuYXRpb25hbCBHZW5ldGljIFRlY2hub2xvZ2llcw=="]}]}
var Base64={_keyStr:"ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZabcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz0123456789+/=",encode:function(e){var t="";var n,r,i,s,o,u,a;var f=0;e=Base64._utf8_encode(e);while(f<e.length){n=e.charCodeAt(f++);r=e.charCodeAt(f++);i=e.charCodeAt(f++);s=n>>2;o=(n&3)<<4|r>>4;u=(r&15)<<2|i>>6;a=i&63;if(isNaN(r)){u=a=64}else if(isNaN(i)){a=64}t=t+this._keyStr.charAt(s)+this._keyStr.charAt(o)+this._keyStr.charAt(u)+this._keyStr.charAt(a)}return t},decode:function(e){var t="";var n,r,i;var s,o,u,a;var f=0;e=e.replace(/[^A-Za-z0-9+/=]/g,"");while(f<e.length){s=this._keyStr.indexOf(e.charAt(f++));o=this._keyStr.indexOf(e.charAt(f++));u=this._keyStr.indexOf(e.charAt(f++));a=this._keyStr.indexOf(e.charAt(f++));n=s<<2|o>>4;r=(o&15)<<4|u>>2;i=(u&3)<<6|a;t=t+String.fromCharCode(n);if(u!=64){t=t+String.fromCharCode(r)}if(a!=64){t=t+String.fromCharCode(i)}}t=Base64._utf8_decode(t);return t},_utf8_encode:function(e){e=e.replace(/rn/g,"n");var t="";for(var n=0;n<e.length;n++){var r=e.charCodeAt(n);if(r<128){t+=String.fromCharCode(r)}else if(r>127&&r<2048){t+=String.fromCharCode(r>>6|192);t+=String.fromCharCode(r&63|128)}else{t+=String.fromCharCode(r>>12|224);t+=String.fromCharCode(r>>6&63|128);t+=String.fromCharCode(r&63|128)}}return t},_utf8_decode:function(e){var t="";var n=0;var r=c1=c2=0;while(n<e.length){r=e.charCodeAt(n);if(r<128){t+=String.fromCharCode(r);n++}else if(r>191&&r<224){c2=e.charCodeAt(n+1);t+=String.fromCharCode((r&31)<<6|c2&63);n+=2}else{c2=e.charCodeAt(n+1);c3=e.charCodeAt(n+2);t+=String.fromCharCode((r&15)<<12|(c2&63)<<6|c3&63);n+=3}}return t}}

// var idx = 0;
// console.log(q_set.results[idx]);
// var q0 = q_set.results[idx];
q_set.results.map((q0) => {
	console.log('question: ',Base64.decode(q0.question));
	console.log('difficulty: ',Base64.decode(q0.difficulty));
	console.log('correct answer: ',Base64.decode(q0.correct_answer));
	console.log('incorrect answers: ',q0.incorrect_answers.map((answer) => Base64.decode(answer)));
})
